

# TRAORE SAFIATOU

STUDENT IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Ivorian, 21 years old with a bachelor's degree in web development and currently a first year in computer engineering. I am looking for 2 months internship starting in june to perfect my skills. Passionate, invested and with a team spirit, i would like to become a Data Scientist. This program will be a great opportunity to learn more about technology and the World.



+216 51 76 93 08



Safiatout95@gmail.com



Tunis Ariana, Tunisia



www.linkedin.com/in/traoresafiatou-9257a31b5

# **EDUCATION**

2021 - in progress Tunis Ariana, Tunisia

2018-2021 Abidjan, Ivory coast

# First Year in Common: ICT Engineering

Private Higher School of Technologies & Engineering (TEK-UP University) Course in Computer and Engineering Mathematics

# **Bachelor of Web Technology and Digital Images**

African Higher School of ICT (ESATIC)

Course in web Development, Infographics and Digital Marketing

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

03/2021 - 06/2021 Abidjan, Ivory coast

10/2020 - 12/2020 Abidjan, Ivory coast

# JUNIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER AT BETSALEEL TECHNOLOGIE (BTECHCI)

Internship (3 months)

- Development of a crowdfunding platform
- Optimisation of the graphic aspects of the website
- Design database

### **COMPUTER ASSISTANT AT IVOIRE TRADER**

Internship (2 months)

- IT Asset Management
- Computer maintenance
- Participate in the development of the E-commerce website

# **PROJECTS**

### INPLEMENTATION OF A COLLABORATION PLATFORM TEAM OF 3 PERSONS

- Identification of needs
- Design
- Full stack developement

#### INPLEMENTATION OF A RECYCLING PLATEFORM FOR PRINTING WASTE

### **SKILLS**

# **TECHNICAL**

**PYTHON** DATABASE

DESIGN/ORACLE

HTML/CSS/JS

PHP



LINUX **UNBUTU** 

# **LANGUAGES**

**SOFT SKILLS** 

✓ Dvnamic

✓ Serious

✓ Spirit of analysis

French: native English: fluent

# **INTERESTS AND ACTIVITIES**

- Student representative: African Higher School of ICT (ESATIC)
- Computer club member: Private Higher School of Technologies & Engineering (TEK-UP University)